[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following maxims, meaning The people rule, is the official state motto of Arkansas?", "correct_answer": "Regnat populus", "incorrect_answers": ["Esto perpetua", "Dirigo", "Ditat Deus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A large mantis can feed on birds or small mammals.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This American writer and teacher became the first woman US Senator, although she occupied the position for only one day.", "correct_answer": "Rebecca Latimer Felton", "incorrect_answers": ["Jeanne  Rankin", "Hatie Caraway", "Nellie  Taylor Rose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are more males then females in a pride.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Hollywood actor starred in the 2006 movie Blood Diamond?", "correct_answer": "Leonardo DiCaprio", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Cruise", "All of these", "Johnny Depp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of these movies but one, star Wallace Reid, considered to be one of the most attractive actors of the silent era.", "correct_answer": "Racing Hearts", "incorrect_answers": ["The Dictator", "Thirty Days", "Whats Your Hurry?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This show is credited by the Guinness Book of World Records as being the longest-running soap opera. Its 15,000th episode aired on September 7, 2006.", "correct_answer": "The Guiding Light", "incorrect_answers": ["Days of Our Lives", "General Hospital", "One Life to Live"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song by Irish band U2 contains the line, Blue-eyed boy meets a brown-eyed girl?", "correct_answer": "The Sweetest Thing", "incorrect_answers": ["The One", "Beautiful Day", "Elevation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cheirognomy is part of chiromancy, or palm reading. What is the object of its study?", "correct_answer": "The mounts of the palm", "incorrect_answers": ["The fingers", "The feet and toes", "The fingernails"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Beatles first #1 hit on the US Billboard charts was I Want to Hold Your Hand.  What was their second #1 hit?", "correct_answer": "She Loves You", "incorrect_answers": ["Hey Jude", "Cant Buy Me Love", "Yesterday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what popular animated movie did Matthew Broderick voice the character Simba the lion?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The Lion King II: Simbas Pride", "The Lion King", "The Lion King 1 1/2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This aircraft entered service with the United States Navy in 1999.", "correct_answer": "F/A18 Super Hornet", "incorrect_answers": ["F-15 Eagle", "E-3 Sentry", "F-16 Fighting Falcon"]}]